No one survives in the suicide forest.
Grave Halloween is a tv movie, horror, science
fiction film directed by Steven R. Monroe.
After inadvertently unleashing an ancient curse, a documentary crew of American exchange
students is haunted by angry spirits in Japan's infamous Suicide Forest.
Amber, played by Cassi Thomson.
Kyle, played by Graham Wardle.
Maiko, played by Kaitlyn Leeb.
Brody, played by Jesse Wheeler.
Skylar, played by Tom Stevens.
Terry, played by Dejan Loyola.
Grave Halloween (also known as The Suicide Forest and released in some
markets as Deathly Halloween) is a 2013 Canadian TV horror film.
An original production by CineTel Films for Syfy, it was directed by Steven R.
Monroe and written by Ryan W.
Smith and Sheldon Wilson.
The film is set in Japan, but it was filmed in Canada.
The film explores themes of suicide, college, forest, evil spirit, tokyo, japan.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.